But in one of the implications of our chief, which is generous,
Heavenly Father, we're blessed to live in a place where we can come together
and be part of the business of our community.
We'll just be with us all the night.
Guide to discussion.
Give our leaders wisdom and the decisions they make.
So in your name, we pray.
Amen.
I'd like to lead you to the light of the United States of America.
And to the Republic for which it stands.
One nation under God made it as a role.
We'll believe we're here in the SSR now.
Four above the gift letter.
Let's get to the personal taxes.
Five.
Times lists.
Most of the way through.
Second.
render or build for the review and response to emails to the administration and with our
attorneys for the review of current violence over that previous month. The budget, though that we
have in place more than covers these costs, if this was to be approved, the remaining balance
of that budget for those I would be $657,000 and $649.
Thank you most to approve. Second.
Parker?
Hi.
Sandra?
I'm Sandra.
Williams?
Hi.
Sample?
Hey, the new business of any of which is residents of both of you this agenda.
9 staff reports.
10 trustee community announcements.
11.
we'll be continued from Council chambers to be in the staff room for the purpose of executive
session at the completion of the regular meeting for the moment to be Council.